{
    "id": "5169afb07d714477bbeba02ec31b6a72",
    "title": "Prepositions After Particular Words And Expressions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Those glasses belong …………………. the top shelf.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d0166507387a4c04a56ec7e23dac1d45"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was angry ………………… . him for lying to her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f370b473703a42269b950970e2d2ad9b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is not particularly good ……………….. football.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c4a56266d8da40b7afc18caf20e9573d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The manager said that he would like to see a big increase ………………….. productivity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "of",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "87726b6b01184f1f838109b4beaa08ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t want to spend the rest of my life fighting …………………. the tax office.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "58ade28187104e43a7ab518877f6da2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was driving carelessly, and crashed ……………… the car in front.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "against",
                "into",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8f8f3e8f833a46fd9a8c150451f34c4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was quite disappointed ………………….. my results.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "about",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "4d4b2accd9b3492eb83a0a19628d5ebc"
        },
        {
            "question": "When the chairman ………………….. the room everybody stopped talking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "entered",
                "entered into",
                "entered at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7d6be6c5ca784d308c94d63eeab91197"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our firm has just ………………… an agreement with them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "entered",
                "entered with",
                "entered into"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bcb0238c7daa47f39813ac2d5e12cf16"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are lacking ……………….. tact.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b4cab7450a7b4859aa628976cc85f1c1"
        }
    ]
}